<resources>
    <string name="app_name">RunCoach</string>
    <string name="rest">\n Tips: \n Take the day off \n \n You can also take this day to do active recovery such as swimming \n </string>
    <string name="recovery">\n Tips : \n A recovery run is a relatively short run performed at an easy pace. \n \n Recovery runs are best done the day after a hard run. \n \n Example: 4 miles easy \n</string>
    <string name="base">\n Tips: \n A base run is a relatively short to moderate-length run at a runner’s natural pace. \n \n Base runs will make up a bulk of your weekly training mileage \n \n Example: 6 miles at natural pace \n</string>
    <string name="long_run">\n Tips: \n The function of a long run is to increase raw endurance. \n \n The distance or duration required to achieve this effect depends on current level of endurance. \n \n Example: 15 miles at natural pace \n</string>
    <string name="progression_run">\n Tips \n A progression run is a run that begins at a runner’s natural pace and ends with a faster segment at anywhere from marathon down to 10K pace. \n \n Example: 5 miles at natural pace + 1 mile at marathon pace + 1 mile at half-marathon pace \n</string>
    <string name="fartlek">\n Tips: \n A fartlek workout is a base run that mixes in intervals of varying duration or distance. \n \n Example: 6 miles at natural pace with 10 x 1:00 pickups at 5K pace with 1:00 recoveries mid-run \n</string>
    <string name="hill_repeats">\n Tips: \n Hill repeats are repeated short segments of hard uphill running. \n \n  Example: 10 x 45-second hill repeats at a hard effort with 2-minute jogging recovery between reps \n</string>
    <string name="tempo">\n Tips: \n A tempo run is a sustained effort at lactate threshold intensity, which is the fastest pace that can be sustained for 20 minutes. \n \n Example: 1 mile of easy jogging (warmup) + 4 miles at lactate threshold pace + 1 mile of easy jogging (cooldown) \n</string>
    <string name="intervals">\n Tips: \n Interval workouts consist of repeated shorter segments of fast running separated by slow jogging or standing recoveries. \n \n Example: 1 mile of easy jogging (warmup) + 5 x 1K at 5K race pace with 400m jogging recoveries + 1 mile of easy jogging (cooldown) \n</string>
    <string name="toggle_action">TOGGLE</string>

</resources>
